Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Press Releases and Public Outreach Materials, 1954-1959, 1973-2022 (bulk 1983-2022) IA10011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Press releases, subject files, 1974-2002; 2006; Series II.; 7.08 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
  - J. Paul Getty Museum:
    - Museum departments:
      - Paintings:
        - Dosso Dossi, Court Painter in Renaissance Ferrera, on view at the Getty Center, April 27, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - Tiepolo Acquisition, February 1, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 161)
        - Cezanne Acquisition, November 30, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 162)
        - Sarah Siddons Portraitists, June 18, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 163)
        - Dosso Dossi Acquisition, January 15, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 164)
        - Monet Acquisition, November 12, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 165)
        - Ed Ruscha's Light, April 23, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 166)
        - Poussin Acquisition, April 17, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 167)
        - Cezanne Still Life Acquired, May 16, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 168)
        - Fra Bartolommeo's Renaissance Painting Acquired "Rest on the Flight into Egypt with St John the Baptist,", May 10, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 169)
          [Note: includes Response to Press Accusation 5/14/1996 and Press Clipping]
        - Acquisitions of Monet, Millet, Gericault, and Degas, September 25, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 170)
        - The Earl and Countess of Arundel: Renaissance Collectors, February 16, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 1)
        - Rembrandt's The Abduction of Europa and Daniel and Cyrus Before the Idol, January 31, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 2)
        - Rogier van der Weyden's Madonna and Child, May 25, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 3)
        - Gilding the Dome of Heaven: Gold Ground Paintings in Medieval and Renaissance, August 6, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 4)
        - Picturing the Ancient World: Antique Revival Paintings, April 12, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 5)
        - Titian's Venus and Adonis, June 18, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 6)
        - Van Gogh's "Irises,", March 21, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 7)
        - Manet's "Rue Mosnier with Flags,", November 14, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 8)
        - Pontormo's portrait of Cosimo I de' Medici, May 31, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 9)
        - Renoir's "La Promenade" Purchased, April 5, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 10)
        - Ensor's "Christ's Entry into Brussels in 1889,", November 18, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 11)
        - Mantegna's "Adoration,", February 9, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 12)
        - Purchase of Ensor's "Christ's Entry into Brussels in 1889,", October 8, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 13)
        - Mantegna's "The Adoration of the Magi" Purchased, April 18, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 14)
        - Armand Hammer Collection Exhibit 9/13/1977 to 10/19/1977 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 15)
          [Note: includes 7/25/1977 Release (1 duplicate copy); 9/6/1977 Press Preview (1 duplicate copy); 9/8/1977 Release; Invitation to Lecture; Summary of Lecture; Public Service Announcement (1 duplicate copy)]
        - Painting Conservation Exhibit 3/30/1976 to 5/29/1976 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 16)
      - Photographs:
        - Photographs of David Octavius Hill and Robert Adamson, exhibition on view at Getty Center, July 20-October 10, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - Edgar Degas, photographs on view at Getty Center, February 2-March 28, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - Brassai: The Eye of Paris, on view at the Getty Center, April 13, 1999-July 3, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - William Eggleston 10/26/1999-1/30/2000, September 15, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 17)
        - Nadar and Warhol, June 28, 1999; March 19, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 18)
        - Important Gifts of Photographs, March 29, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 19)
        - Daguerreotypes, March 27, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 20)
        - David Hockney Acquisition, August 7, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 21)
        - The Eye of Sam Wagstaff, November 18, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 22)
        - Julia Margaret Cameron 10/15/1996-1/0/1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 23)
        - Roger Fenton: The Orientalist Suite, June 24, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 24)
        - Doris Ulmann: Photography and Folklore, March 4, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 25)
        - The Magic of Material Things: Albert Renger-Patzsch, December 6, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 26)
        - Photography Exhibitions: Alfred Stieglitz: Seen and Unseen, September 1, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 27)
        - Laszlo Moholy-Nagy Centennial Exhibition of Photographs 5/15/1995 and Book: In Focus 6/27/1995, May 15, 1995; June 27, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 28)
        - Two Releases for Carrie Mae Weems: Hidden Witness: African Americans in Photography, January 10, 1995; February 16, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 29)
        - Hidden Witness: African-Americans in Early Photography, December 2, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 30)
        - Frederick Sommer Explores 50 years of Photography, October 25, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 31)
        - Early 20th Century Pictorialist Photography in California, August 17, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 32)
        - Andrew Kertesz Exhibit, March 8, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 33)
        - "Pallette of Light: Handcrafted Photographs, 1898-1914", January 3, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 34)
        - Big Exhibit of "Little Pictures", September 10, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 35)
        - Women Photographers Exhibit, May 28, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 36)
        - Edmund Teske Exhibit, March 17, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 37)
        - Fame and Photography, January 20, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 38)
        - Camille Silvy's "River Scene, France,", October 14, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 39)
        - Manuel Alvarez Bravo: Recuerdo de unos anos, June 26, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 40)
        - Two Lives: O'Keeffe by Stieglitz, 1917-1924, April 6, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 41)
        - Manuel Alvarez Bravo Photographs Acquired, February 20, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 42)
        - Walker Evans: An Alabama Record, January 24, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 43)
        - Gift from Graham and Susan Nash, November 25, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 44)
        - Grave Testimony: Photographs of the Civil War, October 31, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 45)
        - Atget's Magical Analysis: Photographs, 1915-1927, August 8, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 46)
        - Lisette Model: Daring to See, May 14, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 47)
        - August Sander: Faces of the German People, March 26, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 48)
        - Neither Speech nor Language: Photography and the Written Word, December 18, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 49)
        - Domestic Idylls, Photographs by Lady Hawarden, October 4, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 50)
        - Paul Strand: People and Place, July 12, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 51)
          [Note: includes Duplicate copies of Release, Copy of Advance Press Information, Partial List of Works on View, and Request for Photographic Services]
        - Persistent Themes: Notable Photography Acquisitions, April 11, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 52)
        - Carleton Watkins: Western Landscape and the Classical Vision, January 16, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 53)
        - Experimental Photography: The New Subjectivity, October 26, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 54)
        - Experimental Photography: The Machine Age, August 7, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 55)
        - Experimental Photography: The Painter Photographer, May 2, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 56)
        - Experimental Photography: The First Golden Age, February 14, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 57)
        - 150 Years of Photography Surveyed, November 15, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 58)
        - After the Manner of Women: Photographs, July 27, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 59)
        - Gustave Le Gray Photography Exhibit, March 15, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 60)
        - Eternal Cities: Photographs of Athens and Rome, December 11, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 61)
        - Alexander Rodchenko: Modern Photography in Soviet Russia, September 29, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 62)
        - Images that yet/Fresh images beget… Photographing Art, July 21, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 63)
        - Rate States and Unusual Subjects: Strand/Kertesz/Ray, May 14, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 64)
        - Flowering of Early French Photography, March 6, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 65)
        - Procession to the Fallen Gods: Photography in 19th Century Egypt, December 23, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 66)
        - Edward Weston's Los Angeles Period, October 23, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 67)
        - Whisper of the Muse: Photographs by Julia Margaret Cameron, July 10, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 68)
        - Holdings of New Department of Photographs, June 8, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 69)
        - New Department of Photographs Announced, June 8, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 70)
        - Archaeological Photography 1865-1914: 11/14/80 to 2/15/81, October 24, 1980 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 71)
        - CalArts Impressions of the Getty 11/1/1980, October 24, 1980 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 72)
        - Venice Restored Exhibit 10/20/1979 to 1/1980 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 73)
          [Note: includes Schedule of Lectures, Venetian Lecture Series, Biography of Rollin van Nostrand Hadley and The Campaign to Save Venice, Details of Coordinated Lectures with LA County Museum of Art, Early Details of Exhibit, and Correspondence Regarding Planning Exhibit and Background of Exhibit]
        - Museum Photography Exhibit through 6/28/1976 to 9/3/1976, June 21, 1976 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 74)
      - Sculpture and Decorative Arts:
        - Adriaen De Vries Imperial Sculptor on view at the Getty Center, Foundry to Finish in Studio of Adriaen De Vries, October 12, 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        - Drapery and Costumes in European Drawings from 15th – 16th Century Exhibition, December 4, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 35)
        - Exhibition of 16th Century Ornamental Designs, April 22, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 36)
        - Intention to Acquire "The Three Graces" by Antonio Canova, September 24, 1993; (includes photograph) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 15)
        - The Corner Cupboard by Dubois: A Closer Look, February 21, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 37)
        - Gallery of European Silver, July 1, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 38)
        - Silver Gallery Opens 5/1988, April 13, 1987; June 1, 1988,; July 1, 1988; (1 copy each of three separately dated releases) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 39)
        - French Decorative Arts Exhibit, January 3, 1979; January 16, 1979,; April 10, 1978; (1 copy each of three separately dated releases) (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 40)
        - 18th Century France: The Height of Fashion 1/19/1976 to 4/19/1976, January 10, 1976 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 41)
        - Rodin's Rodin, December 10, 1975 (Box 2007.IA.34-2, Folder 42)
    - Performances and events:
      - Family Fun (Spanish and English), May 3, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 115)
      - Literary Readings of Selected Shorts 10th Season, June 7, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 124)
      - Poetry at the Getty, January 29, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 125)
      - Free Concert Series: Sounds of LA, January 5, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 126)
      - Fred Astaire Tribute, November 23, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 127)
      - Media Advisory: Meredith Monk and Lila Downs Concert, September 27, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 128)
      - Media Advisory: Exploring Fame and Celebrity, September 14, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 133)
      - Friday Nights at the Getty: Media Advisory (includes Press Coverage Invitation), September 10, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 129)
      - Gordon Getty Concert Series, June 22, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 130)
      - The Affliction of Glory: A Comedy about Tragedy, June 18, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 131)
      - Family Festival (English and Spanish), 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 116)
        [Note includes: Media Advisory for 10/3/1999, Invitation to Press for 7/10/1999, and Other Media Advisories (1999)]
      - Media Advisory: Friday Nights at the Getty 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 132)
      - The Art of Collecting: The Earl and Countess of Arundel, July 7, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 134)
      - "Day without Art" Observed December 1, 1994, November 14, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 135)
      - Programs for Families Fact Sheet 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 117)
      - Notice to Editors: Stephen Garrett Public Lecture on Villa's 20th Anniversary, December 16, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 136)
      - Education Spanish Family Activities, December 11, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 118)
      - Family Program on February 24, 1990, January 8, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 119)
      - A Day without Art, November 23, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 137)
      - Honoring Samuel Wagstaff as part of "A Day without Art", November 16, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 138)
      - Museum Visitors Talk Back, November 16, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 139)
      - Family Programs on November 11, 1989 and December 9, 1989, November 2, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 120)
      - Family Program on April 22, 1989, April 6, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 121)
      - "Tuesday Club" Children's Art Workshops, December 12, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 122)
      - Free 1986 Summer Children's Classes, June 26, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 123)
    - Fellows, Scholars and Visiting Conservators:
      - $100,000 in Fellowships to 10 Curators in US and Europe, May 25, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 102)
      - Curatorial Research Fellowships Grant Program, September 7, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 103)
      - 1993-94 Guest Scholars and Visiting Conservators Named, June 14, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 75)
      - 1992-93 Guest Scholars and Visiting Conservators, July 30, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 76)
      - 1991-92 Visiting Conservators and Scholars, April 10, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 77)
      - 1990-91 Guest Scholars, May 30, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 78)
      - 1990-91 Visiting Conservators, June 4, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 79)
      - 1989-90 Visiting Conservators, June 12, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 80)
      - 1988-89 Guest Scholars Announced, May 13, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 81)
      - 1988-89 Visiting Conservators, May 13, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 82)
      - 1987-88 Guest Scholars, May 21, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 83)
      - 1987-88 Visiting Conservators, May 21, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 84)
      - 1986-87 Guest Scholars, May 15, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 85)
      - 1986-87 Visiting Conservators, May 15, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 86)
      - Historical Lists of Getty Scholars and Speakers, 1973-1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 112)
        [Includes: List of guest scholars by program year and nationality 1978-1988; List of speakers 1973-1986; List of visting scholars and lecturers from United Kingdom 1974-1988]
    - Graduate interns:
      - List of 1996-1997 Graduate Interns (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 178)
        [Note: Includes Request for Housing Letter and Application 6/7/1996]
      - List of 1995-1996 Graduate Interns (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 179)
      - Housing Sought for Student Interns, June 1, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 155)
      - List of 1994-1995 Graduate Interns (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 180)
      - 1994-1995 Graduate Student Programs, August 3, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 170)
      - 1993-1994 Graduate Interns, June 14, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 162)
      - 1993-1994 Graduate Student Programs, September 8, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 171)
      - 1992-1993 Graduate Interns, July 30, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 163)
      - Housing Sought for Student Interns, June 29, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 157)
      - 1992-1993 Graduate Student Programs, July 9, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 172)
      - Housing Sought for 1991-1992 Student Interns, July 9, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 158)
      - 1991-1992 Graduate Interns, July 9, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 164)
      - Housing Sought for 1990-1991 Student Interns, August 7, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 159)
      - 1991-1992 Graduate Student Programs, August 3, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 173)
      - 1990-1991 Graduate Interns Announced, August 3, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 165)
      - 1990-1991 Graduate Student Programs, July 18, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 174)
      - 1989-1990 Graduate Interns, July 18, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 166)
      - Housing Sought for Sudent Interns, June 29, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 160)
      - 1989-1990 Student Programs, July 22, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 175)
      - 1988-1989 Graduate Interns, September 6, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 167)
      - Housing Sought for Student Interns, July 21, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 161)
        [Note: includes Press Release, 5/15/1988 letter to Friends of the Getty Museum and Intern List, and 7/22/1988 copy of an advertisement placed in Aviso]
      - 1988-1989 Student Programs, July 2, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 176)
      - 1987-1988 Student Assistants and Interns, May 21, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 168)
      - 1987-1988 Student Programs, August 13, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 177)
      - 1986-1987 Student Interns and Assistants, May 15, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 169)
    - Volunteers and docents:
      - Getty Seeks Volunteer Docents, March 29, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 144)
      - Getty Seeks Volunteers, November 1, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 145)
      - Getty Seeks Docents and Volunteers, April 26, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 146)
      - Volunteer Opportunities, April 9, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 147)
      - Volunteers Sought, April 5, 1995; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 148)
      - Volunteers and Docents Sought (English/Spanish), March 23, 1993; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 149)
      - Volunteers and Docents Sought (English and Spanish), March 11, 1992; March 20, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 150)
      - Recruitment for Orientation Docents (Spanish and English), July 18, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 151)
      - Recruitment for Orientation Docents (Spanish and English), July 12-13, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 152)
      - Recruitment for Orientation Docents, July 21, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 153)
      - Recruitment for Orientation Docents, June 4, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 154)
  - Getty Conservation Institute (GCI):
    - Appointments, awards, and resignations:
      - Timothy Whalen Named Director, December 15, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 79)
        [Includes communications plan and resumes]
      - GCI, Getty appoints Timothy P. Whalen as Director of the Getty Conservation Institute, December 15, 1998 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
      - Miguel Angel Corzo Resigns, November 30, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 80)
      - GCI, Miguel Angel Corzo resigns as Director of the Getty Conservation Institute, November 30, November 30, 1998 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
      - GCI, Miguel Angel Corzo receives UNESCO medal during General Assembly in Paris, October 21, 1997 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        [Includes correspondence]
      - Giora Solar Appointed Special Projects Director, January 31, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 81)
      - President Clinton Names Miguel Angel Corzo to Committee, January 30, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 82)
      - Miguel Angel Corzo Appointed Director, November 20, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 83)
      - Miguel Angel Corzo appointed Director of Special Projects, September 3, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 84)
      - Luis Monreal Appointment, January 21, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 85)
        [Includes: Curriculum Vitae and LA Times Press Clipping]
      - Marta del la Torre Named Training Program Director, October 16, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 86)
    - Conferences:
      - St. Petersburg, 1993-1996:
        - The Getty Conservation Institute/St Petersburg Preservation Center, January 23, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 51)
        - International Preservation Center opens, June 19, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 52)
        - Media Advisory: St. Petersburg International Center for Preservation, June 19, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 53)
        - Project Fact Sheet: St. Petersburg International Center (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 54)
        - Preventive Conservation Conference in St Petersburg, June 10, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 55)
      - Mediterranean, 1995:
        - International Conference on Mediterranean Archaeological Sites, May 12, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 56)
        - International Conference on Conservation of Archaeological Sites, May 4, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 57)
      - Adobe 90, 1990:
        - Press Kits, October 1, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 58)
          [Note: Includes Release on Conservation of Earthen Architecture (10/1/1990); Laboratory and field Research on adobe; Background information on individuals; Papers scheduled for presentation; Event schedule; Photos]
        - Pitch Package/Materials (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 59)
          [Note: includes: Sample packet sent to journalists including actual samples of adobe, Registration card, and pitch letter; Program material in French; Update announcement; Change in venue announcement; Post conference tour information]
        - General Correspondence and Notes/Incoming (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 60)
          [Note: Includes Planning meeting for possible projects; Publicity outline; Assorted correspondence; Alphabetical list of sites and monuments in GCI Special Projects; Editorial introduction; Experimental design for a test wall project at Fort Selden; Conference goals]
        - General Correspondence and Notes/Outgoing (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 61)
          [Note: Includes Assorted correspondence; Publicity outline; Pitch packets and press kits; Press badge list; Pitch letter; List of attendees]
        - Pitch Package/Correspondence: Pitch Letters (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 62)
        - Photographic Material/Permissions (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 63)
        - Press Relations/Clippings (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 64)
      - GCI, Mortality Immortality conference at Getty Center, March 25-27, 1998 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        [Note: Includes Participant list; Conference session descriptions]
    - Exhibitions:
      - Landmarks of a New Generation, 1994-1996
        - GCI, Picture Mexico City: Landmarks of a New Generation, photography exh. at Museo Rufino Tamayo, Mexico City, September 4-October 26, 1997 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
          [Note: Includes project overview and interviews]
        - Picture Mumbai: Landmarks of a New Generation, January 13, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 74)
          [Note: Includes Press release; Photo sheets; Press kit folder (The kit includes one of each of the following: GCI mission statement; Information sheet on landmarks; Information sheet on Genesis; Quotations by the photographers; Biographies of the photographers; Biographies of Miguel Angel Corzo and Dr. Mahasti Afshar)]
        - Picture Cape Town: Landmarks of a New Generation, August 23-November 8, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 75)